OMPHALUS KUA

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Email: haluskua.one@gmail.com **Phone:** +64 225732261 **Website:** https://serviceman.netlify.app **Github:** https://www.github.com/haluskua **Linkedin:** https://www.linkedin.com/in/haluskua-77/

Job Objective

To take a challenging role as Front End Web Developer in a highly technical company that will allow me to grow and utilize my skills to affirm a certain confidence and experience within the industry. I want to be the best at my skills.

Technical Skills:

- I have a firm understanding of the current web industry standards
- Great with HTML, CSS, Javascript, Canvas, Flex Box, Grid styles, Bem
- Certified Fullstack developer with ReactJs, NodeJs, Express, GraphQl,
- Dealing with APIs, Redux, Redux Toolkit
- Proficient with Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, AdobeXD, and Figma
- Building WordPress sites with Elementor template builder

Soft Skills:

- Building good relationships with clients
- Profound ability to work independently and with a team
- Patience + determination
- Accountability and Acknowledgement
- Time management
- Listening skills
- Play and work balance
- Quality of friendliness

Work Experience:

Pecxer Financial Services: 2018 - current

- Created and Monitored content of the website and assisted the Director in the Web Content Editing process.
- Google Analytics Search Engine Optimization
- Email and social media Marketing

Khanakhazana Indian Restaurant: 2020 - 2021

- Online Food ordering website for Indian Takeaway business
- Facebook marketing

Education:

Enspiral Dev Academy: 2019

- Certified Fullstack Developer
- 700+ hours of coding
- Frontend lead on the final project
- Simulated work environment Agile/waterfall, git, and scrum master

Yoobee School of Design: 2016

- Diploma in Web design
- Fundamentals of web design: Wireframes, HTML, CSS, Jquery, Php, JavaScript, and WordPress
- Client e-commerce website as final year project

Wellington Institute of Technology: 2009 - 2014

- Bachelor in Creative Technology: Major in digital media
- Graphic design, 3d modeling, character design, motion graphics
- Diploma in Exercise Science

Semi-pro Rugby League player: 2008

- Elite sport contract
- Team player

I ENJOY

• Updating my skills set and knowledge through online courses & Youtube videos to keep up to date with tech trends. I also love hanging with family, playing guitar, walking/camping, and painting.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Represented my country Papua New Guinea to play against the Australian Kangaroos in an international test match in 2007.
- 1st place in a national art competition in PNG in 1996
- Being a single dad for more than a decade

REFEREES

Peter Mwaimwangi Pecxer Financial Services Ltd

Contact details available on request